[MUSIC]
[음악]
So now we have some training data and some desk data.
훈련 데이터와 테스트 데이터가 나왔습니다
And what we can do next is #Build,
다음으론 #회귀 모델
there's a sub-header here,
여기 서브헤더 넣고
#Build the regression model.
#회귀 모델 만들기입니다
So GraphLab Create has many algorithms pre-implemented for
GraphLab Create는 다양한 기계학습 작업을 위한
various machinery and tasks or you can implement your own if you like.
알고리즘을 구현해 놨는데 원한다면 스스로 구현할 수도 있습니다
And during the sequence of the specialization,
이 특화과정을 진행하면서
you're gonna write many algorithms of your own, but for this course,
많은 알고리즘을 짜보게 될 것이지만
we're just gonna use pre-implemented algorithms so
이 강의에서는 이미 구현된 알고리즘을
can really try to understand how machine learning works.
통한 기계학습 이해에 집중할 겁니다
So what you can do with machine learning?
기계학습으로 뭘 할 수 있죠?
So, we're gonna do is a build a square foot prediction model.
평수 예측 모델을 만들 수 있습니다
Just call it sqft_model.
sqrt_model이라 부르죠
And in GraphLab, there something called linear regression.
GraphLab에는 선형회귀라는 게 있습니다
So, linear regression is what we learned, what we explored and
선형회귀는 에밀리와 함께 학습, 탐구, 이해까지
talked about, and we understood quite well during the module that Ann was teaching.
이전 모듈에서 마쳤죠
And so if you just say linear _regression.create,
linear_regression.create이라 입력하면
it's going to create a linear regression model for you.
선형회귀 모델을 생성합니다
That creates the traits with projects GraphLab Create, and
Create은 프로젝트의 이름인 GraphLab Create임과 동시에
create is also the verb to use to create various things with GraphLab Create.
GraphLab Create에서 뭔가를 만들 때 쓰는 함수이기도 합니다
So we're now going to create a linear regression model, and
선형회귀 모델을 만들텐데
what I have to give as input I give it the training data.
입력으로 훈련 데이터를 넣습니다
So here's the training data.
훈련 데이터죠
You have to say what variable you're trying to predict.
뭘 예측하는지 변수를 지정해줘야 합니다
So that's the target.
그게 대상이죠
So I'm gonna say the target is going to be price.
대상은 가격입니다
So I'm trying to predict price.
가격을 예측합니다
And the question is what are the features, what is the input.
특징이 뭔지도 입력합니다
So, I'm going to say that the features, and by the way, you can use top complete
특징을 입력할 때 함수 파라미터에도
even if [INAUDIBLE] parameters of function, which is pretty cool.
탭 자동완성을 사용할 수 있습니다
So, the features is a list of the features.
특징에는 특징 리스트를 넣어주고요
If you don't give anything, it will use all features, all columns of the data.
아무 것도 안 넣어주면 모든 특징과 모든 열의 데이터를 사용하게 됩니다
But here, the only feature input we want to use is square feet of living space.
지금은 입력할 특징은 전용면적 하나입니다
And that is a string that I need to put in, so
문자열 변수를 넣어야 하는데
I forgot to put it in quotes, so let me fix that real quick here.
따옴표를 잊었네요 빨리 고치죠
So open quotes,
따옴표를 열고
close quotes.
닫습니다
All right, very good.
됐습니다
So let me just reread that for us.
다시 읽어드리죠
So sqft_model graphlab.linear_regression.create on
sqft_model은 graphlab.linear_regression.create에
the training data to predict the target price using features sqft of living.
훈련 데이터를 넣고 전용면적 특징을 통해 대상 가격을 예측합니다
Let's go an execute this.
실행해보죠
On training data training, I wrote data twice here.
훈련 데이터에서 데이터를 두 번 적었네요
You see the arrow came out here, training data and the score data.
여기 오류가 발생했죠 훈련 데이터 밑줄 데이터
So now let's execute.
다시 실행합니다
So what's happening here?
어떻게 됐죠?
It's done actually, but what we did was create a linear regression model,
선형회귀 모델을 생성했는데
it used a particular algorithm called Newton's Method.
뉴턴 방법이란 알고리즘을 사용했습니다
But GraphLab Create chooses an algorithm automatically for
GraphLab Create는 특별한 지정이 없는 이상
you unless you tell it which one to use.
알고리즘을 자동으로 선택합니다
And this algorithm allows you to make some predictions on the data.
이 알고리즘은 데이터에 대한 예측을 할 수 있게 해주죠
[MUSIC]
[음악]